const test = {
  title: "IELTS Listening  9",
  audioUrl: "https://example.com/audio/test2.mp3",
  sections: [
    {
      section: 1,
      audioUrl: audios.lis9Part1,
      parts: [
        {
          part: 1,
          title: "Oz Housesitters-home Owner Registration Form",
          questions_range: "Questions 1-10",
          description: "Write ONE WORD AND/OR A NUMBER for each answer.",
          type: "note_completion",
          questions: [
            {
              prompt: "Name:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 1,
                  text: "Jenny Hall",
                },
              ],
            },
            {
              prompt: "Address:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 1,
                  text: "14 1) * @ * St Greenfield",
                },
              ],
            },
            {
              prompt: "Mobile no:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 2,
                  text: "2) * @ *",
                },
              ],
            },
            {
              prompt: "Date required from:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 3,
                  text: "3) * @ * ",
                },
              ],
            },
            {
              prompt: "Length of time required:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 4,
                  text: "4) * @ * weeks",
                },
              ],
            },
            {
              prompt: "House features:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 5,
                  text: "-	it has a new 5) * @ *",
                },
                {
                  number: 5,
                  text: "-	it is near a station",
                },
                {
                  number: 6,
                  text: "-	there is room for the housesitter’s 6) * @ *",
                },
              ],
            },
            {
              prompt: "Special duties required:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 7,
                  text: "-	water the 7) * @ * tree",
                },
              ],
            },
            {
              prompt: "Housesitter requirements:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 8,
                  text: "-	the house is large so a 8) * @ * is preferred.",
                },
                {
                  number: 9,
                  text: "-	no 9) * @ * allowed",
                },
                {
                  number: 10,
                  text: "-	would like a check carried out by the 10) * @ *",
                },
              ],
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      section: 2,
      audioUrl: audios.lis9Part2,
      parts: [
        {
          part: 1,
          title: "Questions 11-16",
          description:
            "Choose the correct letter A, B, or C.Becoming a millionaire",
          type: "multiple-choice",
          questions: [
            {
              number: 11,
              question:
                "Arthur feels that when starting a business, mistakes should be ",
              type: "multiple-choice",
              options: [
                "seen as an opportunity to learn.",
                "predicted and minimised.",
                "avoided at all costs",
              ],
              answer: "Library",
            },
            {
              number: 12,
              question: "Recent American studies found that confidence will ",
              type: "multiple-choice",
              options: [
                "sometimes reduce people's chances of success",
                "be increased by reading self-help books.",
                "ensure good results on business courses.",
              ],
              answer: "Library",
            },
            {
              number: 13,
              question:
                "The American studies recommended that new entrepreneurs",
              type: "multiple-choice",
              options: [
                "listen to their colleagues' advice.",
                "get professional help when things go wrong.",
                "remain concentrated on their aims",
              ],
              answer: "Library",
            },
            {
              number: 14,
              question:
                "What does Arthur say about his own experience of marketing?",
              type: "multiple-choice",
              options: [
                "He relied on what he already knew",
                "He hired an expert to take care of it.",
                "He realised its importance too late.",
              ],
              answer: "Library",
            },
            {
              number: 15,
              question:
                "What does Arthur think Is an important quality shared by good leaders?",
              type: "multiple-choice",
              options: [
                "They are ambitious for their company.",
                "They can deal with difficult people.",
                "They earn the respect of their workforce.",
              ],
              answer: "Library",
            },
            {
              number: 16,
              question: "What does Arthur say about taking risks?",
              type: "multiple-choice",
              options: [
                "He advises being cautions.",
                "He favours a long-term view.",
                "He believes it is financially advantageous",
              ],
              answer: "Library",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          part: 2,
          title: "Questions 17-18",
          question:
            "Which TWO things does Arthur say people should focus on when developing their business idea?",
          description: "Choose TWO letters, A-E",
          type: "matching",
          items: [
            "making sure the idea is original",
            "offering a better deal than competitors",
            "being committed to it",
            "paying attention to detail",
            "fixing realistic prices",
          ],
          questions: [
            {
              number: 17,
              option: "",
              answer: "A",
            },
            {
              number: 18,
              option: "",
              answer: "B",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          part: 2,
          title: "Questions 19-20",
          question:
            "Which TWO things does Arthur say helped him get his business started?",
          description: "Choose TWO letters, A-E",
          type: "matching",
          items: [
            "family support",
            "getting a loan from a bank",
            "good business advice",
            "a favourable economic climate",
            "an effective approach to business",
          ],
          questions: [
            {
              number: 19,
              option: "",
              answer: "A",
            },
            {
              number: 20,
              option: "",
              answer: "B",
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      section: 3,
      audioUrl: audios.lis9Part3,
      parts: [
        {
          part: 1,
          title: "Questions 21-26",
          question: "What is said about each of the following experiments?",
          description:
            "Choose SIX answers from the box and we the correct letter, A-H next to questions 21- 26",
          type: "matching",
          items: [
            "making sure the idea is original",
            "offering a better deal than competitors",
            "being committed to it",
            "paying attention to detail",
            "fixing realistic prices",
          ],
          questions: [
            {
              number: 21,
              option: "Steam engine",
              answer: "A",
            },
            {
              number: 22,
              option: "Breakfast cereals",
              answer: "B",
            },
            {
              number: 23,
              option: "Bouncing balls",
              answer: "A",
            },
            {
              number: 24,
              option: "Making paper",
              answer: "B",
            },
            {
              number: 25,
              option: "Tie-dyeing",
              answer: "B",
            },
            {
              number: 26,
              option: "Glue from milk",
              answer: "B",
            },
          ],
        },
        {
          part: 2,
          title: "",
          questions_range: "Questions 27–30",
          description:
            "Label the diagram below. Write the correct letter, A-G, next to questions 27-30.",
          type: "map",
          image: imges.img9,
          questions: [
            {
              number: 27,
              option: "Metal container",
              answer: "A",
            },
            {
              number: 28,
              option: "Integral strainer",
              answer: "B",
            },
            {
              number: 29,
              option: "Drip to",
              answer: "C",
            },
            {
              number: 30,
              option: "Pottery container",
              answer: "C",
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      section: 4,
      audioUrl: audios.lis9Part4,
      parts: [
        {
          part: 1,
          title: "Office Design",
          questions_range: "Questions 31-40",
          description:
            "Complete the notes below. Write ONEWORDONLY for each answer.",
          type: "note_completion",
          questions: [
            {
              prompt: "Early 20th Century:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 31,
                  text: "-	workers employed to do 31) * @ * were arranged in rows",
                },
              ],
            },
            {
              prompt: "1960s to present:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 31,
                  text: "Variations in design of open-plan offices:",
                },
                {
                  number: 32,
                  text: "-	first, workers had individual 32) * @ *",
                },
                {
                  number: 33,
                  text: "-	later, they had cubicles with high or low 33) * @ *",
                },
                {
                  number: 34,
                  text: "-	nowadays, workers may have to 34) * @ * a work area",
                },
              ],
            },
            {
              prompt: "Survey results",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 35,
                  text: "Attitudes of employees to open-plan designs:",
                },
                {
                  number: 35,
                  text: "-	there is a lack of 35) * @ *",
                },
                {
                  number: 36,
                  text: "and 36) * @ *",
                },
                {
                  number: 37,
                  text: "-	they pose a risk to our 37) * @ * (staff records support this)",
                },
              ],
            },
            {
              prompt: "Attitudes of employers to open-plan designs:",
              question_text: [
                {
                  number: 38,
                  text: "-	they significantly reduce rent and 38) * @ * costs",
                },
                {
                  number: 38,
                  text: "-	they improve teamwork and communication",
                },
                {
                  number: 39,
                  text: "-	they can make 39) * @ * staff easier",
                },
                {
                  number: 40,
                  text: "In reality, employees are unhappy and they are often distracted by the 40) * @ * the office.",
                },
              ],
            },
          ],
        },
      ],
    },
  ],
  answers: {
    1: "Gray",
    2: "0491577248",
    3: "29th September",
    4: "3",
    5: "pool",
    6: "car",
    7: "lemon",
    8: "couple",
    9: "smoking",
    10: "Police",
    11: "A",
    12: "A",
    13: "C",
    14: "B",
    15: "C",
    16: "A",
    17: "B/C",
    18: "C/B",
    19: "A/E",
    20: "E/A",
    21: "B",
    22: "G",
    23: "F",
    24: "A",
    25: "H",
    26: "E",
    27: "D",
    28: "F",
    29: "G",
    30: "C",
    31: "typing",
    32: "desks",
    33: "screens",
    34: "share",
    35: "privacy",
    36: "security",
    37: "health",
    38: "energy",
    39: "training",
    40: "noise",
  },
};

